<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<ARTICLES>
	  <article id="1w2d12p44nadj1qax9ci3mfebe">
      <headline><![CDATA[Lovren ready to rise to Liverpool challenge]]></headline>
      <teaser><![CDATA[Dejan Lovren is determined to win over his doubters as he is set to return to the Liverpool starting XI following Mamadou Sakho's injury.]]></teaser>
      <publishedTime>2015-11-18T10:05:56Z</publishedTime>
      <lastUpdateTime>2015-11-18T10:06:02Z</lastUpdateTime>
      <byLine>Stefan Coerts</byLine>
      <body><![CDATA[<p>Liverpool defender Dejan Lovren has stressed he is ready to prove his worth in the absence of Mamadou Sakho.</p>

<p>Sakho is expected to be out of action for up to two months due to a knee injury he picked up in the loss against Crystal Palace, meaning Lovren is likely to return to the starting XI.</p>

<p>The 26-year-old Croatian lost his starting berth after sustaining an ankle injury earlier this season, but he is ready to go again.</p>

<p>"Mama had a really good couple of games and a good start to the season. We played in Rubin Kazan together and were feeling really good," Lovren told Liverpool's official website.</p>

<p>"But you never know in football - injuries can happen today or tomorrow.</p>

<p>"So you need to be prepared. I was working hard all the time so I'm ready and looking forward to playing."</p>

<p>Lovren has received his fair share of criticism since joining Liverpool from Southampton in 2014 and he is determined to win over his doubters.</p>

<p>"Last year I had a tough year. I didn't do pre-season with the team and everything was such a rush," he added.</p>

<p>"Everyone, all together, has started better than last year. It was important for me that I had a good pre-season with the team and I'm feeling more comfortable now. </p>

<p>"I know the expectations - I know a little bit more about the club and the feelings of the fans. I'm proud to be here. Now my thing is to be here for as long as possible and to win something with the club."</p>
]]></body>
      <seoPageTitle><![CDATA[Lovren: I am ready to prove myself at Liverpool]]></seoPageTitle>
   </article>
	  <article id="2lq9pndbqdi41un1hqykuc70h">
      <headline><![CDATA[Giroud frustrated by France display]]></headline>
      <teaser><![CDATA[After France's 2-0 defeat to England on Tuesday, Olivier Giroud rued a poor performance from the visitors.]]></teaser>
      <publishedTime>2015-11-18T09:49:50Z</publishedTime>
      <lastUpdateTime>2015-11-18T09:49:56Z</lastUpdateTime>
      <byLine>Alex Fisher</byLine>
      <body><![CDATA[<p>Olivier Giroud was left frustrated with France's performance in their 2-0 friendly defeat to England, despite the difficult circumstances surrounding the game.</p>

<p>Goals from Dele Alli and Wayne Rooney settled proceedings at Wembley on a sombre night as football remembered those affected by the terror attacks in Paris last Friday.</p>

<p>Both teams and sets of fans were united in a stirring rendition of La Marseillaise before kick-off, and the subsequent minute silence was impeccably observed by the 71,223-strong crowd.</p>

<p>Once the game got underway, France struggled to find their momentum and Arsenal striker Giroud was left disappointed with their display.</p>

<p>"We are very disappointed that we didn't play well," he said. "Despite the circumstances we had to represent our country the best we could. We were proud to have that opportunity tonight. </p>

<p>"We faced an efficient English side. We struggled against them. It was not really 'us' tonight.</p>

<p>"As soon as we decide to play the game, we are all professional football players and even if it is everything but easy, we must deliver on the pitch. </p>

<p>"As soon as the referee whistled, we should have straight away got into the game. We couldn't do it."</p>

<p>Despite his frustrations, Giroud had no regrets about playing the game.</p>

<p>He added: "We wanted to play that game for all these people who stayed in France. We wanted to pay tribute to the victims' families."</p>
]]></body>
      <seoPageTitle><![CDATA[Olivier Giroud frustrated by France display]]></seoPageTitle>
   </article>
	  <article id="p52luwdfvifn1dls6rsmll6fc">
      <headline><![CDATA[Marsh deserves another chance - Lehmann]]></headline>
      <teaser><![CDATA[Shaun Marsh deserves to get "first crack" in the Australia side after Usman Khawaja was ruled out, coach Darren Lehmann said.]]></teaser>
      <publishedTime>2015-11-18T09:38:12Z</publishedTime>
      <lastUpdateTime>2015-11-18T09:38:17Z</lastUpdateTime>
      <byLine>Peter Thompson</byLine>
      <body><![CDATA[<p>Darren Lehmann says Shaun Marsh has earned the right to replace the injured Usman Khawaja in the third Test against New Zealand.</p>

<p>Marsh was named in a 13-man squad for the final Test of the series in Adelaide next week after Khawaja suffered a hamstring injury, while James Pattinson and Stephen O'Keefe were also drafted in.</p>

<p>Michael Klinger and Glenn Maxwell were overlooked by the selectors despite being in the runs in the Sheffield Shield and Australia coach Lehmann has explained the decision to recall Marsh.</p>

<p>He said: "He was very close in the first Test selection. It was touch and go with Uzzy and Shaun Marsh. And he played really well for us last summer, he got 99 in Melbourne and a got a couple of 50s in Sydney.</p>

<p>"We thought he played quite well in the West Indies when he got his chance as well. He gets another chance to have a crack at Test cricket. He got some runs in Melbourne, which was pleasing to see. He gets first crack."</p>

<p>Lehmann also reiterated that 35-year-old Klinger did not miss out due to age not being on his side.</p>

<p>He added: "I think he's younger than (Adam) Voges isn't he? So age doesn't go against him. There's been a lot of speculation, he's made a lot of runs.</p>

<p>"At the end of the day Shaun Marsh is more recent in Test match cricket and has made a contribution, so that's the way we decided to go.</p>

<p>"Shaun's proven as in he's made some runs and contributions. He'll still want to prove himself again. I still remember that great hundred he got against South Africa at Centurion.</p>

<p>"So as a selection panel it was tight for all those guys when you've got to pick a batter."</p>

<p>Australia lead the series 1-0 heading into the first ever day-night Test, which starts at the Adelaide Oval next Friday.</p>
]]></body>
      <seoPageTitle><![CDATA[Darren Lehmann explans Shaun Marsh Australia recall]]></seoPageTitle>
   </article>
	  <article id="rdw2c69ulg1h1bffu82qlg1es">
      <headline><![CDATA[Neymar still important without goals - Dunga]]></headline>
      <teaser><![CDATA[Dunga feels Neymar still played a big role in Brazil's World Cup qualification win over Peru even if he did not score himself.]]></teaser>
      <publishedTime>2015-11-18T09:17:11Z</publishedTime>
      <lastUpdateTime>2015-11-18T09:17:18Z</lastUpdateTime>
      <byLine>Stefan Coerts</byLine>
      <body><![CDATA[<p>Brazil coach Dunga has defended captain Neymar in the wake of his side's 3-0 World Cup qualification win over Peru.</p>

<p>The Barcelona star was unable to replicate his superb club form at the Itaipava Arena Fonte Nova in Salvador as he was outshone by Douglas Costa.</p>

<p>Bayern Munich winger COsta opened the scoring halfway through the first half before setting up the second and playing a role in Brazil's third goal, too.</p>

<p>Nevertheless, Dunga was quick to stress Neymar was still vital to his team's success.</p>

<p>"Neymar was marked by two or three players, thus creating space for others," the Brazil coach told Globo Esporte.</p>

<p>"Neymar was the one who opened up space for Renato Augusto for the second goal. He did a lot of work and played his part for the team."</p>

<p>The win over Peru saw Brazil climb to third place in the table with seven points from four games and Dunga is optimistic about their chances of reaching the 2018 World Cup.</p>

<p>"We must finish in the top four in order to qualify," he added.</p>

<p>"Everybody has been speaking about how difficult it would be, but the team is growing.</p>

<p>"We climbed from seventh spot to fifth place and now to third. We are on the right track to qualify, which is all that matters."</p>
]]></body>
      <seoPageTitle><![CDATA[Dunga underlines Neymar importance to Brazil]]></seoPageTitle>
   </article>
	  <article id="1tmn55k3fwxyy1h6ijvpw0htxm">
      <headline><![CDATA[Bebe: I have the same style as Cristiano Ronaldo]]></headline>
      <teaser><![CDATA[Rayo Vallecano attacker Bebe feels his playing style is similar to that of Real Madrid superstar Cristiano Ronaldo.]]></teaser>
      <publishedTime>2015-11-18T08:37:01Z</publishedTime>
      <lastUpdateTime>2015-11-18T08:37:07Z</lastUpdateTime>
      <byLine>Stefan Coerts</byLine>
      <body><![CDATA[<p>Former Manchester United attacker Bebe has likened his style to that of Real Madrid star Cristiano Ronaldo, while also voicing his admiration for Didier Drogba.</p>

<p>Bebe has impressed this campaign at Rayo Vallecano after previous disappointing spells with United and Benfica and he believes his style of play is similar to that of his illustrious compatriot.</p>

<p>"My idols? Drogba and Cristiano Ronaldo. I have the same way of running and the same shooting style as Cristiano," Bebe told AS.</p>

<p>"He's definitely one of my favourites."</p>

<p>The 25-year-old failed to make the grade at United after joining from Vitoria Guimaraes in 2010, but he still has fond memories of his time at Old Trafford.</p>

<p>"It all happened very quickly, a total surprise. One day I'm training and the next they]]>&#x2019;<![CDATA[re telling me that I'm going to sign a five-year contract with Manchester United. I thought it was a joke. I wasn't there long, but I enjoyed it," Bebe added.</p>

<p>"It was every kid's dream, it was insane. I was playing with the best in the world. It wasn't easy, the first week I had to take a deep breath, but I got used to it. I adapted and tried to fit in.</p>

<p>"Rio Ferdinand, Ryan Giggs and Wayne Rooney really impressed me. A few months earlier I was watching them on TV and suddenly here I was running, jumping and talking to them. Giggs really caught my attention, I saw how they loved him, always asking for autographs, pictures, jerseys."</p>
]]></body>
      <seoPageTitle><![CDATA[Bebe: I have the same style as Cristiano Ronaldo]]></seoPageTitle>
   </article>
	  <article id="1gk7b89v92bfo1fejfpngiuvv6">
      <headline><![CDATA[No Bundesliga postponement - Rauball]]></headline>
      <teaser><![CDATA[The cancellation of the friendly between Germany and Netherlands due to security fears will not affect this week's Bundesliga action.]]></teaser>
      <publishedTime>2015-11-18T07:50:42Z</publishedTime>
      <lastUpdateTime>2015-11-18T07:50:49Z</lastUpdateTime>
      <byLine>Stefan Coerts</byLine>
      <body><![CDATA[<p>DFL president Reinhard Rauball has made it clear there are no plans to postpone this weekend's round of Bundesliga action in the wake of the cancellation of Tuesday's international friendly between Germany and Netherlands for security reasons.</p>

<p>This week's encounter in Hannover was called off just two hours before kick-off as there were "serious plans to bring about an explosion", just days after last week's game between France and Germany in Paris had been targeted by terrorists.</p>

<p>Terrorist attacks across six locations in Paris, including the Stade de France, killed 129 people on Friday.</p>

<p>Tuesday's events in Hannover had cast doubt over whether this week's Bundesliga action would go ahead as planned, but Rauball has now stressed the games will not be postponed as things stand.</p>

<p>"This weekend's Bundesliga action will go ahead as scheduled," he told DPA.</p>

<p>"The cancellation of the game between Germany and Netherlands has changed football in this country. It was a sad day for football.</p>

<p>"I have nothing but respect for the decision to cancel the game. I know how hard it was to make such a decision. The safety of the people should always be priority number one."</p>

<p>Prior to the cancellation of the game between Germany and Netherlands, Belgium's match against Spain in Brussels, also scheduled for Tuesday, was cancelled due to security fears.</p>

<p>France's match against England at Wembley went ahead, with tributes to the victims of the Paris attacks taking place before kick-off.</p>
]]></body>
      <seoPageTitle><![CDATA[Reinhard Rauball: No Bundesliga postponement]]></seoPageTitle>
   </article>
	  <article id="1tnmfjgxvlklc1sczym2ray8zr">
      <headline><![CDATA[Bangalore Test called called off due to more rain]]></headline>
      <teaser><![CDATA[The second Test between India and South Africa has been called off after more persistent rain on day five in Bangalore.]]></teaser>
      <publishedTime>2015-11-18T07:39:09Z</publishedTime>
      <lastUpdateTime>2015-11-18T07:39:14Z</lastUpdateTime>
      <byLine>Omnisport</byLine>
      <body><![CDATA[<p>Further persistent rain in Bangalore has resulted in the second Test between India and South Africa being called off. </p>

<p>Days two, three and four at the M Chinnaswamy Stadium were washouts, and day five followed suit, with a pitch inspection at around noon local time determining that no play would be possible.</p>

<p>Just 81 overs were bowled on day one, with India bowling South Africa out for 214 then reaching 80-0 in reply.</p>

<p>The hosts lead the four-match series 1-0 ahead of the third Test in Nagpur, which gets under way on November 25.</p>

<p> </p>
]]></body>
      <seoPageTitle><![CDATA[Rain sees India v South Africa cancelled]]></seoPageTitle>
   </article>
	  <article id="14ub3yas54b9e1iy3fth4cfbnm">
      <headline><![CDATA[Parish: Palace hopeful of securing US investment]]></headline>
      <teaser><![CDATA[Crystal Palace co-chairman Steve Parish has revealed the club are in negotiations to secure investment from the United States.]]></teaser>
      <publishedTime>2015-11-18T06:28:10Z</publishedTime>
      <lastUpdateTime>2015-11-18T06:28:15Z</lastUpdateTime>
      <byLine>Tom Beck</byLine>
      <body><![CDATA[<p>The owners of Crystal Palace are hoping to seal a deal with US investors to help improve the financial future of the Premier League outfit.</p>

<p>Co-chairman Steve Parish has revealed the club are in negotiations with David Blitzer and Josh Harris - co-owners of the NHL's New Jersey Devils and the NBA's Philadelphia 76ers - to take an equal 18 per cent overall share of the south London club.</p>

<p>The three other Palace co-owners - Martin Long, Jeremy Hoskings and Stephen Browett - will all see their club shares reduce to 15.33 per cent.</p>

<p>Parish, who believes the investment will make Palace "as strong as it has been for 100 years", will remain in control of the day-to-day running of the club and said improvements to Selhurst Park will be a priority.</p>

<p>"I think this club can be massive and it's a great opportunity," he told the BBC.</p>

<p>"I want to move fast and to do that you need big funds. I'm prepared to do my bit, the three boys who are involved with me are prepared to do their bit.</p>

<p>"But we need to bring some new people in to accelerate it and make sure we've got everything we need. If I was a Palace fan, and I am, I'd be fantastically excited about the future."</p>

<p>Parish, speaking at an event in New York, added: "If this deal doesn't happen the team will be fine.</p>

<p>"But I really want to see the club fulfil the potential it should have fulfilled. We've had our share of bad luck: it's time we put the record straight."</p>

<p>The co-owner, who saved the Eagles from bankruptcy in 2010, is eager for the club to tap into the US market.</p>

<p>"The world began here in football three years ago, so to everybody here we're just a Premier League club - we've managed to erase the rest of our history," Parish joked.</p>

<p>"There is a real buzz about soccer, football, in the US and we need to capitalise on it. So we'll be back and forth here as much as we can trying to grab our fair share of support."</p>
]]></body>
      <seoPageTitle><![CDATA[Parish: Palace hopeful of US investment]]></seoPageTitle>
   </article>
	  <article id="m0rp0j6zugum149m4lnvk4zm9">
      <headline><![CDATA[Klinsmann content with USA draw]]></headline>
      <teaser><![CDATA[The United States and Trinidad and Tobago shared the spoils following a 0-0 draw in CONCACAF World Cup qualifying.]]></teaser>
      <publishedTime>2015-11-18T06:26:50Z</publishedTime>
      <lastUpdateTime>2015-11-18T06:26:56Z</lastUpdateTime>
      <byLine>Sacha Pisani</byLine>
      <body><![CDATA[<p>United States coach Jurgen Klinsmann was satisfied with Tuesday's scoreless draw against Trinidad and Tobago, though he rued his team's wastefulness in front of goal.</p>

<p>Klinsmann's USA shared the spoils with Trinidad and Tobago in CONCACAF World Cup Group C qualifying in the Port of Spain.</p>

<p>USA had chances to claim maximum points on the road, but Gyasi Zardes and Jermaine Jones hit the woodwork.</p>

<p>Speaking afterwards, Klinsmann told reporters: "As expected, it was a tricky game.</p>

<p>"There were chances on both sides, I think we had the better of them]]>&#x2026;<![CDATA[ We should have put one away.</p>

<p>"All in all, a draw on the road is okay. It keeps us at the top of the group as we move towards Guatemala in March."</p>

<p>USA are level alongside Trinidad and Tobago on four points from two matches, but top the standings on goal difference, heading into next year's qualifier against Guatemala.</p>

<p>Klinsmann added: "We want to go into Guatemala in March and get three points, then beat them at home and make it clear were the top team in this group."</p>
]]></body>
      <seoPageTitle><![CDATA[Jurgen Klinsmann content with United States draw]]></seoPageTitle>
   </article>
	  <article id="vmuojsd9w17r178qiybk9zum8">
      <headline><![CDATA[Sanchez critical of Uruguay conduct]]></headline>
      <teaser><![CDATA[Chile forward Alexis Sanchez took to social media after the 3-0 loss to Uruguay to criticise the conduct of their opponents.]]></teaser>
      <publishedTime>2015-11-18T06:26:08Z</publishedTime>
      <lastUpdateTime>2015-11-18T06:26:14Z</lastUpdateTime>
      <byLine>Tom Beck</byLine>
      <body><![CDATA[<p>Alexis Sanchez criticised the behaviour of Uruguay's players after Chile were defeated 3-0 in their World Cup qualifier in Montevideo on Tuesday.</p>

<p>In another bad tempered affair ]]>&#x2013;<![CDATA[ following on from the controversial quarter-final Copa America clash in June ]]>&#x2013;<![CDATA[ seven players were cautioned, whilst Jorge Valdivia was sent off for the visitors after the final whistle.</p>

<p>Taking to social media via Instagram, Sanchez found fault with Uruguay's conduct, insisting they were as bad winners as they were losers.</p>

<p>"It is necessary to be able to win and to lose [well] and I speak when I lose and when I win," the 26-year-old Arsenal forward wrote, accompanied by a picture of his country's 2015 continental success.</p>

<p>"But what bothers me is that current and ex-Uruguay players, and others that I do not even know, speak without recognizing when they lose and that bothers me.</p>

<p>"Today we lost and I them congratulate ... It's goodbye from the champions of the Americas."</p>

<p>Chile fell to their first defeat in CONMEBOL World Cup qualifying, dropping to fifth in the standings after defenders Diego Godin, Alvaro Pereira and Martin Caceres all scored for Uruguay.</p>

<p>Oscar Tabarez's men are up to second, after winning three of their first four matches.</p>
]]></body>
      <seoPageTitle><![CDATA[Sanchez critical of Uruguay conduct]]></seoPageTitle>
   </article>
	  <article id="1rjirkgp0oaja1ugvbhg7cvad1">
      <headline><![CDATA[Defending champ Streb hoping to find form at Sea Island]]></headline>
      <teaser><![CDATA[The 2015 PGA Tour schedule wraps up at the RSM Classic in Georgia, starting Thursday.]]></teaser>
      <publishedTime>2015-11-18T05:25:33Z</publishedTime>
      <lastUpdateTime>2015-11-18T05:25:38Z</lastUpdateTime>
      <byLine>Sacha Pisani</byLine>
      <body><![CDATA[<p>Robert Streb is hoping he can turn his form around as he bids to go back-to-back at the RSM Classic.</p>

<p>Streb broke through for his maiden PGA Tour title after holding off Brendon de Jonge and Will MacKenzie in a play-off to win last year's event, then known as the McGladrey Classic.</p>

<p>While Streb has gone on to perform well at major tournaments since, finishing in a tie for 10th at the PGA Championship, while he was 18th at The Open, the 28-year-old American has struggled this season.</p>

<p>In the three events he has played so far, Streb has missed the cut (Frys.com Open), tied for 53rd (CIMB Classic) and shared 35th (WGC-HSBC Champions), heading into Thursday's opening round at the Sea Island Golf Club.</p>

<p>"You kind of get your confidence going. You get tournaments under your belt and you feel like you can win most weeks," Streb told reporters.</p>

<p>"It is definitely a momentum thing. I may not be playing my best this year but hopefully I can spin it around. I was playing a little bit better heading in last year but obviously done some better things over the past 12 months.</p>

<p>"The resume is probably better. I don't know if I'm playing better at his point but you never know when it is going to turn around."</p>

<p>The 2015 PGA Tour schedule wraps up in Georgia this week, with next month's Hero World Challenge - hosted by Tiger Woods - an unofficial tournament.</p>

<p>Graeme McDowell, Peter Malnati, Zach Johnson, De Jonge and MacKenzie are all in the field.</p>

<p>There is also a father-son combination set to feature at the RSM Classic.</p>

<p>Davis Love III has been paired with son Davis Love IV for the first two rounds.</p>

<p>"It's a great way to do it," said father Love. "It's a comfortable place for him.</p>

<p>"He'll be uncomfortable maybe on the first tee, but I think once we get him off the first tee, get his dad off the first tee, we]]>&#x2019;<![CDATA[ll settle down and have fun."</p>
]]></body>
      <seoPageTitle><![CDATA[Defending champ Streb hoping to find form at Sea Island]]></seoPageTitle>
   </article>
	  <article id="1d11l6ys738fy1nhsxpt437ovd">
      <headline><![CDATA[Neymar could be forced to leave Barcelona, says player's father]]></headline>
      <teaser><![CDATA[Barcelona attacker Neymar could be forced to leave Camp Nou, according to the Brazilian's father.]]></teaser>
      <publishedTime>2015-11-18T05:00:45Z</publishedTime>
      <lastUpdateTime>2015-11-18T05:00:51Z</lastUpdateTime>
      <byLine>Tom Beck</byLine>
      <body><![CDATA[<p>Neymar could be forced to leave Barcelona if his tax evasion case is not resolved, according to the player's father.</p>

<p>A Brazilian court has frozen £31.3million worth of assets belonging to the Barca attacker, his family and related businesses, with the 23-year-old alleged to have evaded £10.5m worth of taxes in Brazil from 2011 to 2013.</p>

<p>Neymar, who has scored 13 goals in 14 appearances for his club side this term, is enjoying a rich vein of form but his father revealed his future at Camp Nou could be jeopardised by the ongoing investigations.</p>

<p>"We are talking about a [contract] renewal but we need to solve some things," Neymar Sr told Cadena SER.</p>

<p>"We need to know if Spain accepts our situation. It's hard for us because we are receiving many attacks, from Brazil and from Spain. Neymar is a star and works his image here and from Brazil.</p>

<p>"We're talking to everyone to know what to do with this matter because we don't want to be in Spain two, three, four, five or 10 years and then we are caught by surprise by saying that our structure is wrong. We need to know if things are right for us.</p>

<p>"We must do the right things and know if Spain let us work. We need to stop these investigations. We want the peace of mind.</p>

<p>"His image is not associated with his job. His image is part of a company in Brazil, which has existed since 2006. It is not now that we've taken advantage of his image.</p>

<p>"For years we've been working with this company. I do not want to talk about persecution but if we don't have a comfortable situation to work we cannot stay in Spain.</p>

<p>"We never had such big fiscal problems in Brazil. After arriving in Spain the attacks began and the attacks have now spread to Brazil. We will respect the contract he has with the club but we don't want a renewal without peace of mind."</p>

<p>Brazil international Neymar still has three years remaining on his contract with Barcelona but has been linked with a move to Premier League side Manchester United in recent months.</p>
]]></body>
      <seoPageTitle><![CDATA[Neymar could be forced to leave Barcelona, says player's father]]></seoPageTitle>
   </article>
	  <article id="1c19begufqtxi19vp8dnnvx958">
      <headline><![CDATA[CONCACAF World Cup Qualifying Review: Costa Rica stay perfect, Jamaica open account]]></headline>
      <teaser><![CDATA[Costa Rica and Jamaica were among the winners in CONCACAF World Cup qualifying.]]></teaser>
      <publishedTime>2015-11-18T04:51:57Z</publishedTime>
      <lastUpdateTime>2015-11-18T04:52:03Z</lastUpdateTime>
      <byLine>Sacha Pisani</byLine>
      <body><![CDATA[<p>Costa Rica continued their perfect start to World Cup qualifying after seeing off Panama 2-1 on Tuesday.</p>

<p>Quick-fire goals from Bryan Ruiz and Marco Urena midway through the second half helped the Costa Ricans make it two wins from as many matches.</p>

<p>Luis Tejada pulled a goal back for Panama with 19 minutes remaining at Estadio Rommel Fernandez Gutierrez but Costa Rica held on to move clear in Group B, three points ahead of the former.</p>

<p>Jamaica were also victorious as they claimed their first win in qualifying via a 1-0 triumph in Haiti.</p>

<p>The Jamaicans lost to Panama last time out but bounced back thanks to English-born Birmingham City striker Clayton Donaldson, who netted the match-winning goal just past the hour-mark.</p>

<p>Guatemala, meanwhile, crushed St Vincent and the Grenadines 4-0 away from home for their first points in Group C.</p>

<p>The United States were held to a goalless draw in Trinidad and Tobago.</p>

<p>In other results, Mexico beat Honduras 2-0, while El Salvador and Canada drew 0-0.</p>
]]></body>
      <seoPageTitle><![CDATA[Costa Rica stay perfect, Jamaica open account]]></seoPageTitle>
   </article>
	  <article id="1olgvkb79emyp1uv0om0e0mt0t">
      <headline><![CDATA[Liverpool CEO Ayre: Gerrard reunion on the cards]]></headline>
      <teaser><![CDATA[LA Galaxy's Steven Gerrard could face his former club for the first time next summer in Liverpool's pre-season tour of the United States.]]></teaser>
      <publishedTime>2015-11-18T03:36:12Z</publishedTime>
      <lastUpdateTime>2015-11-18T03:36:17Z</lastUpdateTime>
      <byLine>Tom Beck</byLine>
      <body><![CDATA[<p>Steven Gerrard could be in line to face Liverpool for the first time next year after chief executive Ian Ayre admitted the club are considering a pre-season tour of the United States in 2016.</p>

<p>Liverpool travelled across the Atlantic in 2014 in preparation for their Premier League campaign and are widely expected to announce a return, which could include a reunion with former captain Gerrard, who left for LA Galaxy at the start of the season.</p>

<p>Ayre has revealed he will discuss the idea with Gerrard prior to the final decision.</p>

<p>"Absolutely, that's something we have on our radar of ideas," he told the BBC.</p>

<p>"Steven is back in Liverpool at the moment and I'm sure we'll get a chance to catch up and see what he thinks about that as an idea.</p>

<p>"It's brilliant we have Steven in the US market, he's been such a great servant to Liverpool and for him to be here - hopefully telling people how great the club is, if they don]]>&#x2019;<![CDATA[t already know.</p>

<p>"That can only be good for us."</p>

<p>Liverpool spent time in Boston, New York, Chicago, Charlotte and Miami on their last tour to the US but Ayre admits the former England skipper's history will be taken into consideration.</p>

<p>"We'll come to the US next summer for certain," he added. "We don't have any information of where. We're trying to look at maybe the west coast, and a little bit of the east coast.</p>

<p>"Typically we've done the east coast in the past so maybe the west coast, but still negotiating with various people and who and where we'll play, but we're always excited.</p>

<p>"We've done it before and always get a great reception, so we look forward to it."</p>
]]></body>
      <seoPageTitle><![CDATA[Liverpool CEO Ayre: Gerrard reunion on the cards]]></seoPageTitle>
   </article>
	  <article id="rs78paljk9p31fl5kdtcemx6v">
      <headline><![CDATA[El Salvador 0 Canada 0: Honours even as De Guzman breaks record]]></headline>
      <teaser><![CDATA[Julian de Guzman made his 85th international appearance in Canada's stalemate in El Salvador on Tuesday.]]></teaser>
      <publishedTime>2015-11-18T03:34:06Z</publishedTime>
      <lastUpdateTime>2015-11-18T03:34:12Z</lastUpdateTime>
      <byLine>Sacha Pisani</byLine>
      <body><![CDATA[<p>Canada were unable to make it two wins from as many World Cup qualifiers after playing out a goalless draw against El Salvador as captain Julian de Guzman became the nation's most-capped player.</p>

<p>De Guzman earned his 85th international cap for Canada in San Salvador on Tuesday, surpassing former international Paul Stalteri.</p>

<p>But Canada were unable to cap the achievement with a win, with Cyle Larin denied by the crossbar in the first half.</p>

<p>Canada were unchanged for the trip to El Salvador, with coach Benito Floro happy to stick with the same XI that beat Honduras 1-0 last week.</p>

<p>El Salvador, on the other hand, made four changes following the 3-0 loss to Mexico as Giovanni Zavaleta, Jaime Alas, Pablo Punyed and Jose Pena came in for Gerson Mayen, Yuvini Salamanca, Diego Chavarria and Rafael Burgos.</p>

<p>The clash was a scrappy affair throughout and it was not until the 34th minute that fans witnessed the first real opportunity.</p>

<p>Dustin Corea found himself in a one-on-one situation with Milan Borjan but the Canada goalkeeper came out on top, getting a hand to the low shot and forcing the ball away for a corner.</p>

<p>Canada had a chance of their own eight minutes later, when Larin beat Henry Hernandez to the ball and saw his header cannon off the crossbar after Junior Hoilett whipped a teasing cross into the penalty area.</p>

<p>The Canadians went close again in first-half stoppage time, Will Johnson firing a long-range strike just over the bar.</p>

<p>There were limited opportunities after the break, as both teams struggled to create anything clear-cut.</p>

<p>Corea, though, had another sight on goal in the 54th minute but Borjan was on hand to deny the FC Edmonton forward.</p>

<p>Canada almost claimed all three points in the first minute of injury time, but Larin's powerful shot hit the side netting.</p>
]]></body>
      <seoPageTitle><![CDATA[El Salvador 0 Canada 0: Honours even as De Guzman breaks record]]></seoPageTitle>
   </article>
	  <article id="11hdljxoajckd1t11z40plql3u">
      <headline><![CDATA[Jedinak full of praise after Socceroos' win]]></headline>
      <teaser><![CDATA[Australia overcame security concerns to rout Bangladesh in World Cup qualifying in Dhaka.]]></teaser>
      <publishedTime>2015-11-18T02:47:09Z</publishedTime>
      <lastUpdateTime>2015-11-18T02:47:14Z</lastUpdateTime>
      <byLine>John Greco</byLine>
      <body><![CDATA[<p>Australia captain Mile Jedinak praised the Socceroos, the team's staff and their fans following the 4-0 drubbing of Bangladesh in Dhaka on Tuesday.</p>

<p>Much of the lead-up to the World Cup qualifier was overshadowed by a number of safety and security concerns in the Bangladeshi capital.</p>

<p>The Socceroos had an unprecedented level of security with them for their whirlwind trip, with Jedinak conceding the whole scenario was a mentally draining experience for the squad.</p>

<p>But Australia got the job done in a professional manner thanks to Tim Cahill's first-half hat-trick to return to the top of Group B with two matches to play following Jordan's shock 1-0 loss to Kyrgyzstan in Bishkek. </p>

<p>"All the build-up, a lot was made about coming here. We showed tonight the focus was there from the get-go," said Jedinak, who was also on the scoresheet.</p>

<p>"It was a great reception, the fans were brilliant, even a few of ours came out which was great to see.</p>

<p>"The boys were clinical in the first half, very patient and we caused them all sorts of difficulties. In open play and at set pieces and we got our breakthroughs.</p>

<p>"The second half our rhythm sort of went a little bit. That's something we need to test ourselves at, when it is 4-0 it's very easy to let go]]>&#x2026;<![CDATA[we didn't let go but a lot of the things weren]]>&#x2019;<![CDATA[t coming off as much.</p>

<p>"Credit to us, we kept at it, we didn't get that fifth goal in the second half but it was a strong away performance."</p>
]]></body>
      <seoPageTitle><![CDATA[Jedinak full of praise after Socceroos' win]]></seoPageTitle>
   </article>
	  <article id="118pdthfvjfkg1jexgj0qcpwet">
      <headline><![CDATA[Brazil 3 Peru 0: Dunga's men punish visitors with solid display]]></headline>
      <teaser><![CDATA[Brazil eased to a 3-0 win over Peru in Salvador after goals from Douglas Costa, Renato Augusto and Filipe Luis.]]></teaser>
      <publishedTime>2015-11-18T02:14:44Z</publishedTime>
      <lastUpdateTime>2015-11-18T02:14:50Z</lastUpdateTime>
      <byLine>Tom Beck</byLine>
      <body><![CDATA[<p>Brazil moved up to third in World Cup qualifying after a 3-0 victory over Peru on Tuesday.</p>

<p>Douglas Costa tapped in Willian's cross from close range and Renato Augusto netted with a calm strike before Filipe Luis sealed all three points in Salvador.</p>

<p>Brazil are now unbeaten in three matches, with Peru falling to ninth place after recording three defeats in their opening four games.</p>

<p>The five-time World Cup winners had lost just three times in 41 appearances against Peru and were eager to improve upon a mixed start to their qualifying campaign.</p>

<p>Brazil took control early, with Dunga's men dominating possession with Willian, Costa and the trickery of Neymar testing Peru's defence.</p>

<p>With 22 minutes played, Costa scored the opening goal of the game following some fine individual skill from Willian.</p>

<p>Collecting the ball on the right of the box, the Chelsea winger played a return pass with Neymar before skipping past two defenders and drilling a powerful cross into the six-yard box for Costa to bundle over the line.</p>

<p>Willian continued to cause danger down the right flank and provided the perfectly weighted pass to Neymar, but the former Santos man struck his vicious volley over the crossbar.</p>

<p>Costa almost doubled the hosts' advantage with a set-piece from an acute angle.</p>

<p>The Bayern Munich star swung a curling effort from near the corner flag over the head of the dumbfounded Diego Penny, but it struck the far post.</p>

<p>Following the interval, Brazil's accurate short passing and possession superiority continued as they made it 2-0 after 57 minutes.</p>

<p>Costa darted into the area from the right flank before supplying Augusto with the opportunity to side-foot past Penny from the edge of the area for his first international goal.</p>

<p>Neymar saw a goal ruled out for offside after poking past Penny as Brazil pushed for a third.</p>

<p>It came with 13 minutes still to play as Costa's drilled strike was parried out by the Peru stopper to the feet of left-back Filipe Luis to tap into an empty net.</p>

<p>Brazil are now 45 World Cup qualifying matches unbeaten at home and have risen three positions with their second win of the campaign, as Ricardo Gareca's men drop below Bolivia on goal difference.</p>
]]></body>
      <seoPageTitle><![CDATA[Brazil 3 Peru 0: Dunga's men punish visitors with solid display]]></seoPageTitle>
   </article>
	  <article id="1uq66qd594z0v1as3xrt5ohiue">
      <headline><![CDATA[Martino relieved after Argentina win]]></headline>
      <teaser><![CDATA[Gerardo Martino could breathe easier after Argentina won for the first time in their 2018 World Cup qualifying campaign.]]></teaser>
      <publishedTime>2015-11-18T01:59:27Z</publishedTime>
      <lastUpdateTime>2015-11-18T01:59:32Z</lastUpdateTime>
      <byLine>Sacha Pisani</byLine>
      <body><![CDATA[<p>Argentina coach Gerardo Martino said he felt joy and peace after the South American giants finally opened their World Cup qualifying account in Colombia on Tuesday.</p>

<p>Lucas Biglia's 20th-minute strike was the difference as Argentina downed Colombia 1-0 to secure their first win on the road to Russia 2018.</p>

<p>Argentina had made a winless start to World Cup qualifying, following their opening loss to Ecuador and back-to-back draws against Paraguay and Brazil, before Biglia's first international goal eased the pressure on Martino.</p>

<p>"I feel joy and peace that we extended what we did with Brazil," Martino said post-match.</p>

<p>"We had one less day of rest and played in an oppressive climate.</p>

<p>"If we lost people were to say that players ran less and did not support the coach, but that was not the case.</p>

<p>"We stood 15 metres further back than usual for a logical fatigue of the temperature, but managed the development of the match."</p>
]]></body>
      <seoPageTitle><![CDATA[Martino relieved after Argentina's qualifying win]]></seoPageTitle>
   </article>
	  <article id="4qvqsax8sr5o18hug82r1nt72">
      <headline><![CDATA[Trinidad and Tobago 0 United States 0: Woodwork denies Klinsmann's men]]></headline>
      <teaser><![CDATA[Trinidad and Tobago tested the United States as the teams played out a scoreless draw in World Cup qualifying.]]></teaser>
      <publishedTime>2015-11-18T01:35:36Z</publishedTime>
      <lastUpdateTime>2015-11-18T01:35:43Z</lastUpdateTime>
      <byLine>Dejan Kalinic</byLine>
      <body><![CDATA[<p>The United States have been held to a 0-0 draw by Trinidad and Tobago in World Cup qualifying on Tuesday.</p>

<p>Fresh from their thrashing of St Vincent and the Grenadines, USA faced a far bigger test at the Hasely Crawford Stadium in Port of Spain.</p>

<p>Gyasi Zardes and Jermaine Jones struck the woodwork and that was as close as the visitors came to making it two from two in Group C.</p>

<p>While Jones' long-range effort was well saved, Zardes perhaps should have scored with his header early in the second half.</p>

<p>Instead, USA shared the spoils to make it four points from two games ]]>&#x2013;<![CDATA[ a record matched by Trinidad and Tobago.</p>

<p>While Jurgen Klinsmann would have preferred a win, he would be pleased with four points ahead of his side's next qualifier in March 2016.</p>

<p>Klinsmann made two changes to his team, with Tim Howard and Michael Orozco replacing Brad Guzan and Bobby Wood.</p>

<p>Stephen Hart did likewise as Cordell Cato and Kevan George came in and replaced Keron Cummings and Lester Peltier.</p>

<p>The hosts started the better of the two teams and Cardiff City man Kenwyne Jones fired wide from 20 yards after a nice turn in the 13th minute.</p>

<p>Cato showed off his pace just before the half-hour mark, getting beyond two markers before scuffing a tough chance wide.</p>

<p>USA had kept possession neatly but struggled to penetrate.</p>

<p>However, the visitors should have gone ahead in the 47th minute.</p>

<p>Jozy Altidore did the hard work down the right before crossing to the back post, where Zardes crushed the crossbar with a free header.</p>

<p>The woodwork denied USA once more in the 78th minute.</p>

<p>Jermaine Jones was given time and space 30 yards from goal and the midfielder's powerful effort was tipped onto the crossbar by Jan-Michael Williams.</p>

<p>That was as close as the visitors came as Trinidad and Tobago pushed for an unlikely winner with no success.</p>
]]></body>
      <seoPageTitle><![CDATA[Trinidad and Tobago 0 USA 0: Woodwork denies Klinsmann's men]]></seoPageTitle>
   </article>
	  <article id="1idl2mfnlr76u1530pnjnvt0fc">
      <headline><![CDATA[Uruguay 3 Chile 0: Godin and Co. exact revenge]]></headline>
      <teaser><![CDATA[Copa America champions Chile lost to Uruguay, who bounced back from their defeat in Ecuador last week.]]></teaser>
      <publishedTime>2015-11-18T01:01:48Z</publishedTime>
      <lastUpdateTime>2015-11-18T01:01:53Z</lastUpdateTime>
      <byLine>Sacha Pisani</byLine>
      <body><![CDATA[<p>Uruguay returned to winning ways with a comprehensive 3-0 victory over South American champions Chile in a fiercely contested World Cup qualifier in Montevideo on Tuesday.</p>

<p>Tempers were running high in the first meeting between the two nations since the infamous coming together of Edinson Cavani and Gonzalo Jara in Chile's quarter-final win at the Copa America in June.</p>

<p>Cavani was controversially sent off for a raised hand to Jara's face after the Chile defender appeared to poke the Uruguay forward in the backside with a finger, which went unnoticed by match officials.</p>

<p>Uruguay, who felt aggrieved afterwards, had the last laugh thanks to Diego Godin and a quick-fire second-half double, ending Chile's unbeaten start to World Cup qualifying.</p>

<p>Godin set the Uruguayans on their way with a 23rd-minute opener - his third goal in qualifying - before substitute Alvaro Pereira and Martin Caceres helped the team bounce back from their 2-1 loss in Ecuador last week.</p>

<p>Making matters worse for the visitors, midfielder Jorge Valdivia was shown a straight red card after the final whistle for apparently verbally abusing the referee.</p>

<p>Uruguay made two changes to the team that went down to Ecuador, with Matias Corujo and Diego Rolan coming in for Alvaro Gonzalez and Abel Hernandez.</p>

<p>Chile coach Jorge Sampaoli also opted to mix it up, drafting in Marcelo Diaz, Mark Gonzalez and Eugenio Mena at the expense of Matias Fernandez, Jean Beausejour and Francisco Silva.</p>

<p>The Chileans started the brighter of the two teams, Arturo Vidal coming close to breaking the deadlock 10 minutes in after almost stabbing in the opener at the near post following Mauricio Isla's sliding ball across the six-yard box.</p>

<p>Emotions threatened to boil over as the half wore on, with Cavani and Jara at it again as both teams came together after Uruguay were awarded a free-kick.</p>

<p>Godin was clearly aggrieved by Chile's treatment of team-mate Cavani and it sparked the skipper into action, the Atletico Madrid star on hand to poke home the close-range opener from the resulting set-piece in the 23rd minute.</p>

<p>Tempers did eventually simmer down in the second half, after Uruguay and Chile squared off again when the referee whistled for half-time.</p>

<p>Chile pushed forward in search of an equaliser but they were continuously met by a wall of Uruguay defenders, Sebastian Coates on hand to cut out Isla's low cross to deny the visitors a goalscoring opportunity 10 minutes into the second half.</p>

<p>At the other end, Pereira had barely been on the pitch for a minute when he headed Uruguay into a 2-0 lead in the 61st minute.</p>

<p>Pereira, who replaced Nicolas Lodeiro, rose highest to loop the ball over Claudio Bravo after Cavani's header had picked out the second-half substitute.</p>

<p>And defender Caceres made sure of the points with a header of his own from a corner kick four minutes later.</p>
]]></body>
      <seoPageTitle><![CDATA[Uruguay 3 Chile 0: Diego Godin and Co. exact revenge]]></seoPageTitle>
   </article>
</ARTICLES>
